http://www.realifewebdesigns.com/policies/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to ReaLifeWebDesigns.com:
We don't ask you for personal information unless we
need it.
We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, ReaLifeWebDesigns.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's visitors use its website. From time to time, ReaLifeWebDesigns.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
ReaLifeWebDesigns.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.
ReaLifeWebDesigns.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, to discourage spammers.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's website choose to interact with ReaLifeWebDesigns.com in ways that require ReaLifeWebDesigns.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that ReaLifeWebDesigns.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with ReaLifeWebDesigns.com are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, ReaLifeWebDesigns.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with ReaLifeWebDesigns.com. ReaLifeWebDesigns.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
ReaLifeWebDesigns.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, ReaLifeWebDesigns.com may monitor the most popular accounts. ReaLifeWebDesigns.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, ReaLifeWebDesigns.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
ReaLifeWebDesigns.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's behalf or to provide services available at ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. ReaLifeWebDesigns.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, ReaLifeWebDesigns.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when ReaLifeWebDesigns.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ReaLifeWebDesigns.com, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a ReaLifeWebDesigns.com website and have supplied your email address, ReaLifeWebDesigns.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with ReaLifeWebDesigns.com and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. ReaLifeWebDesigns.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ReaLifeWebDesigns.com uses cookies to help ReaLifeWebDesigns.com identify and track visitors, their usage of ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's website, and their website access preferences. ReaLifeWebDesigns.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's website, with the drawback that certain features of ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Google Analytics
ReaLifeWebDesigns.com uses Google Analytics and Google Analytics Advertiser features including Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Platform integrations, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to track website user behavior. Google provides an Opt-out Browser Add-on for Analytics here...
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ReaLifeWebDesigns.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Affiliate Marketing
As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, ReaLifeWebDesigns.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in ReaLifeWebDesigns.com's sole discretion. ReaLifeWebDesigns.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a ReaLifeWebDesigns.com account, you should also check the dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
ReaLife WebDesigns - Web Development and Management Services
© 1999-2020 ReaLife WebDesigns. All rights reserved.
home
site map
privacy
terms
